(Raj:)Howard's capsule should be
reentering the atmosphere any minute.
- It'll be good to have him back.
- The Fantastic Four, reunited, ha, ha.
(Sheldon:)You had a good run, fake Wolowitz.
(Sheldon:)We'll remember you
with nostalgic fondness...
(Sheldon:)...the way we do the dial-up modem...
(Sheldon:)...the VHS tape,
or Leonard's gym membership.
(Raj:)We're not kicking him out.
(Raj:)- Stuart and I have become good friends.
- Okay, one vote for, one vote against.
(Sheldon:)- Leonard, you're the tiebreaker.
- I don't have a problem with Stuart.
He gives us a 20 percent discount
at his comic book store.
(Sheldon:)Well, I don't sell
my friendship that cheaply.
- I can go 30.
- Welcome aboard, old chum.
Okay, the NASA website says
Howard's final descent has begun.
(Sheldon:)He left a boy.
(Sheldon:)He returns a boy-sized hero.
(Dimitri:)Loops, calm down!
- What's that?
- The Jewish prayer for eating bread!
(Howard:)We don't have one
for falling out of space!
(Howard:)We did it.
(Howard:)We're on the ground.
We survived!
(Mike:)That was just the parachute.
(Mike:)We still have another six miles to go.